var data = [
  {
    "category": "Happy",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is happy?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is happy?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is happy?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is happy?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "C"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Upset",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        //add pictures
        "question": "Which person is upset?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        //add pictures
        "question": "Which person is upset?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        //add pictures
        "question": "Which person is upset?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        //add pictures
        "question": "Which person is upset?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "B"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Excited",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is excited?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is excited?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is excited?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is excited?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "A"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Neutral",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is neutral?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is neutral?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is neutral?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        //add pictures
        "question": "<p>Which person is neutral?</p><ol><li>A</li><li>B</li><li>C</li><li>D</li></ol>",
        "answer": "C"
      }
    ]
  }
];